-Marumo, wake up. -Huh? What happened?
（薫）マルモ起きて。 （護）んっ？　んっ　何　どうしたの？
Tie my hair.
（薫）薫の髪　結んで。
What?
えっ？
Kaoru, put down your ransel first. Today's Sunday.
薫　まず　ランドセル下ろそうか。 今日はね　日曜だからね。
No, today's Sunday visit. Remember, I gave you the flyer?
違うよ　今日　日曜参観。 プリント渡したじゃん。
Flyer?
プリ？
Oh, Sunday visit.
あっ　日曜参観。
Marumo, let's go. We're gonna be late.
マルモ行くよ　遅刻しちゃう。
-Oh, I give up. -Tomoki, you too. Hurry.
あっ　もういいや　もう。 友樹も　ほらほら。
Let's go, let's go.
行こう　行こう　よし　行こう　おい。行くよ。
To buy things, we need money.
（杉下）物を買うには お金が要りますね。→
To earn that money, people have various occupations.
そのお金をもらうために　みんな 色々な　お仕事をしています。
Our family is pan-ya-san*. *(pan-bread, ya-shop)
（女の子）うちはパン屋さんです。
Yes, pan-ya-san is one too.
（杉下）そう パン屋さんも　そうですね。→
Then what other ya-san are there? Anyone know?
じゃ　他に 何屋さんがありますか。　分かる人。
-Cake-ya-san. -Osushi-ya-san.
（女の子）ケーキ屋さん。 （男の子）おすし屋さん。
Soba*-ya-san. (*Japanese noodle) -Pizza-ya-san.
（男の子）そば屋さん。 （男の子）ピザ屋さん。
Gambari*-ya-san. (*someone who tries very hard)
（友樹）頑張り屋さん。
Tere*-ya-san. (*Shy person; has nothing to do with stores, but ends with ya-san)
照れ屋さん。
Okay, okay, okay.
（杉下）はい はい　はい　はい　はい　えっ→
I thought I heard tere-ya-san just now, but oh well...
今　照れ屋さんとかって 聞こえたけど　まあ　いいか。→
Then besides shops and stores
じゃあ　お店屋さん以外に→
what other jobs are there? Does anyone know?
どんな　お仕事があるか 分かるかな？
I think school teacher is a job too.
学校の先生も お仕事だと思います。
That's right. There are not only shops,
（杉下）そうですね お店屋さんだけじゃなく→
but teachers earn money by educating everyone.
先生も　みんなに勉強を教えて お金をもらう　仕事ですね。→
Okay, I'm going to give you homework now.
じゃあ　これから　みんなに１つ 宿題を出します。
Starting now, you are all members of the job exploration team.
（杉下）今から君たちは お仕事調査隊の隊員です。→
Find out anything you can about
お父さんや　お母さんの お仕事について→
your father or your mother's job.
どんなことでもいいから 調べてきてください。→
You'll be reporting on it at the next class.
今度の授業で 発表してもらいますからね。
-Hello. -Hello. Takagi-san?
もしもし。 [TEL]（かな）もしもし　高木さん？
Kana-san, what's up?
かなさん　どうしました？
Are you free today?
[TEL]今日　これから空いてますか？
Of course I'm free as can be, but what is it?
そりゃ　もう　空きっ放しですけど 何か。
Then how about meeting me for lunch?
[TEL]だったら　これから ランチでも　どうですか？
Yes, of course.
はい　もちろん行きます。
It's good.
（かな）うん　おいしい。→
What were you doing this morning?
今日は 午前中　何やってたんですか？
Oh, today was the day of Sunday visit.
あっ 今日は日曜参観だったんです。
-Sunday visit. -Oh, um...
（かな）日曜参観。 あっ　え～と　いや→
Sun... I made a quick visit.
にち…　一応　参加したんです。
There was a bazaar in the neighborhood, so I dropped in for a visit.
近所でバザーがあって 一応ね　参加を　バザーです。
That sounds like fun.
（かな）え～　楽しそう。→
It's important to get along with your neighbors, isn't it?
ご近所付き合いとかも 大事ですもんね。
Well, yes...
ええ　まあ。
When I opened the window, suddenly I see Yonesuke*. (*TV personality)
窓を開けたら　いきなり ヨネスケが歩いてるんですもん。
What? -With his huge rice scoop.
（かな）えっ？ でっかい　しゃもじ持って。
-Really? -Really, it's true.
（かな）ホントですか？ ホント　ホント。
I was so nervous he was going to make a dash at me.
いつ突撃されるのかって 冷や冷やもんでしたよ。
Oh, and I also saw that guy...that...
あっ　あと　あの人　見たな　あの…。
Atou Kai*.(*Actor) -Ah, yes.
阿藤　快。 （かな）あっ　はいはい。
He was eating dumplings at the neighborhood shopping district.
近所の商店街で 団子　食ってました。
Oh my, Atou-san. Are you making a side trip?
あっ　あらあら　阿藤さん 寄り道ですか？
-Kana-san? -Yes?
あっ　かなさん？ えっ？
-Takiguchi Junpei*? (*voice actor) -Yes.
滝口　順平？ はい。
So you do things like impersonation too.
かなさん 物まねなんてするんですね。
Oh dear, how embarrassing. I'm sorry.
やだ　ちょっと　どうしよう すいません。
Oh?
あら？
Hello?
もしもし？
Marumo?
[TEL]マルモ？
What's wrong, Kaoru?
薫　どうした？
We're hungry.
[TEL]おなか　すいたよ。
Hungry? What about school lunch?
おなかって　給食は。
School was only half day. We don't get school lunch on Sunday visit days.
[TEL]学校は　午前中で　おしまい。 日曜参観は給食なしなの。
-Really? -Hurry up and come home.
そうなの？ [TEL]早く帰ってきて。
Seriously. Okay, just wait.
もう。 分かった　ちょっと待ってろ。
I'm coming home now, okay?
なっ　すぐ戻るから。
Kana-san, I'm sorry. A neighbor just called
かなさん　すいません。 ご近所から電話で→
and asked me to come back to the bazaar.
ちょっと　バザーの方に 戻ってくれって言われちゃって。
Oh, I guess we've been talking for a while now.
（かな）えっ　あっ　ホント。 結構　おしゃべりしてましたね。→
-I'm sorry. -That's alright.
すいません。 いえ。
I'll see you at the office tomorrow.
じゃ　また　あした　会社で。
Yes. I'll e-mail you later.
はい。 あっ　あの　後でメールしますね。
I'll be waiting.
待ってます。
See you then.
（かな）それじゃ。
Marumo-san. What's your job, Marumo-san?
マルモさん マルモさんのお仕事は？
-What ya-san are you? -Wait, wait a minute.
何屋さんですか？ ちょっ　ちょっと待ってなさいよ→
Let me change first.
今　着替えちゃうからさ。
What ya-san are you?
何屋さんなんですか？
Alright, I'm a bunbougu*-ya-san. (*stationery) You guys use them too.
もう　文房具屋さんです。 あなたたちも使ってるでしょ→
Notebooks, erasers, and pencils. Right?
ノートに消しゴム　鉛筆に下敷き ねっ。
-Thank you. -I work for Akebono Office Supplies
あっ　ありがとうございます。 はい。　あけぼの文具の→
in a department called Customer Service.
お客様相談室ってところに 働いてます。
-Customer Service? -Yes.
相談室？ うん。
It's not a store?
お店屋さんじゃないの？
How should I say this?
えっ？ なっ　何て言えばいいんだ？
Um...You know, when customers use things like notebooks and pencils?
え～　あっ　あの　お客さんがね ノートとか鉛筆　使うだろ？
And when they don't understand something or find something wrong,
で　何か分かんないこととか 不便だなって思ったときに→
they call our department.
電話をかけてくるところです。
-I don't get it. -No.
よく分かんない。 嘘。
Yes, it's an e-mail from Kana-san.
[TEL]（メールの着信音） はい。　かなさんからメールだ。
You're a bunbougu-ya-san, but you don't sell anything?
文房具屋さんなのに マルモは売る人じゃないの？
I'm busy right now. Ask me later.
今　忙しいからな うん　後にしなさい。
-How much do you get paid? -How much?
お給料は　いかほど？ いかほど。
Probably not much.
（ムック）大して もらってないだろ。
Be quiet. It's the important part right now.
うるさいな。 今　大事なところなんだよ。
I'll tell you later. Later. Later. Later. Okay?
それね　後でな 後で　後で　後で　はい。
Aw~. But we don't get what you do.
え～。 だって　よく分かんないんだもん。
Oh, I want to go see Marumo's office.
そうだ マルモの会社に行ってみたい。
You know that's impossible. They don't know
そんなの駄目に決まってんだろ。 お前らのことは→
about you guys at work.
秘密になってんだから　会社では。
But Manami-chan said she's going to visit her daddy's office.
でも　まなみちゃん　パパの会社 見に行くって言ってたよ。
We do what we do, and other people do what they do.
うちは　うち　よそは　よそなの。
But it's our homework.
でも宿題だよ。
Then use your imagination and write something up.
じゃあさ イマジネーションで書きなさいよ。
Make a virtual trip to my workplace. Do it virtually.
エア職場見学をしなさい。 エアでしなさい。
I don't get it. Tomoki, let's go.
意味　分かんない。　友樹　行こう。 うん。
Shoot, I made a mistake. I wrote virtual.
間違っちゃった。 エアって書いちゃった。
-What should we do about our homework? -We don't have anything to write about.
宿題どうしよう。 書くこと　なくなっちゃったね。
-Here you go... -Welcome.
（彩）お待たせしました…。 （陽介）はい　いらっしゃい。
That's so unbecoming, a grown man walking around with a cell phone in one hand.
（陽介）何だ　お前　いい大人が 携帯　片手に　みっともねえな。
-Are you e-mailing? -You're here again? It's Sunday, you know.
（真島）メールですか？ お前　今日も来てるの？　日曜だぞ。
He's been drinking since before dark.
（陽介）こいつな 夕方から飲んでるんだ。
You must have lots of free time.
暇だね。
Who are you e-mailing?
（彩）誰とメールしてるんですか？
Oh, Kana-san.
あっ　かなさんなんですけど。
Kana-san is the person I'm currently dating...
あっ　かなさんっていうのは　現在 僕が　お付き合いをしている…。
An idol-like presence at Akebono Office Supplies,
あけぼの文具のマドンナ的存在→
PR Department's Makimura Kana-san, right? I'm quite tired of hearing about her.
広報部の牧村かなさんでしょ？ 聞き飽きましたよ。
Who would have thought that Takagi-san would be going out with her.
（真島）この高木さんが まさか付き合えるとはね。
Yeah, she's beautiful and she's like The Woman Who Can Do It All
ねっ　すっごい美人だし ザ　できる女って感じよね。
Oh, have you met her, Aya-san?
あれ 彩さん会ったことあるんですか？
Just briefly.
（彩）うん　ちらっと。
But you're prettier, Aya-san.
でも　彩さんの方が奇麗ですよ。
Hm? What?
（彩）んっ？　何？
Nothing.
何でもないです。
So what did she say in her e-mail?
それで？　メールには 何て書いてあったんですか？
She said "Lunch was fun today, wasn't it?"
「今日はランチ楽しかったですね」 って。
-You were with her today too? -You'd think they see enough of each other at work every day.
今日も会ってたんですか？ 会社で　毎日　会ってるでしょうに。
What? What? But
えっ？　えっ？　だって→
isn't that what going out with someone is all about?
付き合うって そういうことでしょ？
Isn't it? Huh?
違う？　んっ？
Oh, sorry. Say, how should I reply to this?
あっ　ごめんなさい。　あっ　ねえねえ ねえ　何て返せばいいの　これ。
-When did you get it? -About 2 hours ago.
それ　いつ来たんです？ ２時間ぐらい前。
You ignored it for 2 hours?
２時間も放置してんの？
But I didn't know what to say.
えっ　だって分かんないんだもん。
I've been entering and deleting, entering and deleting all this time.
もう　ず～っと　さっきから 打っては消し　打っては消しだよ→
-For 2 hours. -It doesn't matter what you say.
もう２時間。 何でもいいんですよ。
All she wants to do is chit chat so
相手は 雑談したいだけなんですから→
-just reply appropriately. -That appropriately is the difficult part.
適当に返せば。 その適当が難しいんだろ→
-Dummy, you dummy. -Ouch.
バカ　もう　バカ。 （真島）痛い　もう。
Acting so silly.
浮かれちゃって。
But I'm surprised she understood your situation with the twins.
でも　よく双子のことまで 受け入れてくれましたよね。
Well, um... I haven't told her about the twins yet.
あっ　いや 双子のことは　ちょっと　まだ。
What? You haven't told her about the kids yet?
おい　何だよ　お前　子供たちのことまだ　話　してないのか。
Hey. I don't care if you let her get to your head, but
おいおい のぼせるのは構わねえけどな→
shouldn't you be placing the kids first? They're not something that should be hidden.
一番　大事なのは　子供たちだろ？ 隠すようなことじゃねえぞ。
Yes, I know that.
それは分かってます　はい。
Hey, you're gonna be late. Wake up.
おい　遅刻するぞ　起きなさい。
No school today.
今日は　お休みだよ。
-Why? -To switch the day off with Sunday visit day.
何で？ 日曜参観の振り替え休日。
Switch?
振り？
You guys are so lucky.
うわ～　お前ら　いいな。
Anyway, I'm going. Eat your food, okay?
俺　行くからな。 ちゃんと食べんだぞ。
-Don't sleep in too long. -Okay~.
いつまでも寝てんじゃねえぞ。 （薫・友樹）は～い。
Okay, I'm going then.
よし　じゃ　いってきま～す。
See you later~.
（薫・友樹）いってらっしゃ～い。
Time to start the job exploration.
お仕事調査隊　出動です。
If we follow Marumo, we'll get to Akebono Office Supplies.
マルモの後をついていけば あけぼの文具である。
Make sure he doesn't notice us.
絶対に気付かれないように。
-Roger. -Tomoki, let's go.
ラジャー。 友樹　行くよ。
He's buying something.
あっ　何か買ってる。
If this goes in on the first try,
これが１発で入れば→
Kana-san and I will get closer.
かなさんとの仲が より　いっそう　深まる。
That was practice. Just practice.
今のは練習　今の練習。
We'll get closer.
より　いっそう　深まる。
Ah~ Seriously.
あ～　もう。
-Really. -He stinks.
もう。 下手くそ。
-Oh, crap. -He's running. Tomoki, let's go.
ヤベえ。 走った　友樹　行くよ。
Roger.
ラジャー。
We're gonna lose Marumo.
マルモ　行っちゃうよ。
Don't worry, he'll be back.
大丈夫　戻ってくるよ。
Huh? Where did it go? Huh?
あれ？　ない　あれ？ あれ？　あれ？
Why now of all times.
何で　こんなときに　もう。
-Did you see which button? -Perfect.
ボタンの場所　見えた？ ばっちり。
That was close.
ヤベえ　ぎりじゃん。
We're finally here.
やっと着いた。
-Good morning. -How do we go in?
おはようございます。 どうやって入るの？
What should we do?
どうしよう。
Tomoki, let's go.
友樹　行くよ。
Where does Marumo work?
マルモのお仕事どこだろう。
Not here, huh?
いないね。 うん。
-Is Marumo there? -Found him.
マルモいる？ いた。
He's studying hard. He's great, isn't he?
真面目に勉強してる。　偉いね。 うん。
Ah, yes. Yes, I'm very sorry.
あっ　はい。 はい　申し訳ございません。
What happened? Looks like Marumo's getting scolded.
どうしたんだろ。 マルモ　怒られてるみたい。
Poor Marumo.
かわいそう。
Why are they here.
何で　あいつら。
Wait, Takagi-san. Where are you going all of a sudden?
（真島）ちょっ　ちょっと高木さん 急に　どこ行くんですか？
-Just to the bathroom. -What?
いや　ちょっとトイレ。 えっ？
Hey, guys. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
ちょっ　お前ら。 おい。　おい　おい　おい　おい。
What are you guys doing?
お前ら何してんだよ。
We're doing the job exploration.
お仕事調査隊です。
Did you follow me?
お前　ついてきたのか？
Don't be reckless, exploration team.
無茶すんなよ　調査隊。
But that's our homework and we wanted to see you at work.
だって宿題だから　マルモのお仕事見たかったんだもん。
Hey, hide.
おい　ちょっと隠れて。
Good morning.
お疲れっす。
What should I do with these.
どうすっかな　これ。
We're sorry. We'll go home now.
ごめんなさい　もう帰るよ。
It's not that simple. I can't let you guys go home alone.
簡単に言うなよ ２人きりじゃ危ねえだろ。
You guys, come here. Come, come.
お前ら ちょっ　ちょっと来い　来い　来い。
Light, light.
電気　電気　電気。
Listen, guys. Stay here for a while.
お前ら　いいか？ しばらくは　ここで　じっとしてろ。
Okay, got it.
うん　分かった。
I'll come back first chance I get and take you home.
隙見て戻って すぐに　お前ら送って帰るから。
Hang in there until I come, okay?
それまで我慢だ　なっ。
Seriously, please don't leave this room.
頼むから　絶対　出んなよ。
Okay, we'll do our best.
うん　頑張る。
Okay. Later.
よし　じゃ。
What took you so long?
（真島）ずいぶん　かかりましたね。 んっ？
Oh, I'm having stomach problems.
あっ　腹　壊しちゃってさ。 （真島）えっ？
It's an emergency. Maybe I should go to the hospital.
緊急事態だよ。 病院　行った方がいいのかな。
Yeah. I'm going to the hospital just to be on the safe side.
うん 念のため　病院　行ってくるわ。
-No, I'll take you. -What's going on?
（真島）いえ　俺　送りますよ。 （民子）どうしたの？
-Takagi-san has a stomach ache. -Are you alright?
高木さん　腹　痛いって。 えっ　大丈夫ですから。
I can go by myself. I'm a grown man, you know.
１人で行けますから。 大人ですから。
No, shouldn't someone go with you?
（鮫島）いや 行った方がいいんじゃないか？
But there aren't any hospitals close by.
（民子）でも 近くに病院なんかないわよ。
-Isn't it an emergency? -Huh? No...well...
緊急事態なんでしょ？ んっ？　いや　んっ　そっ→
Oh, it feels like it's settling down.
あっ　あら？ 何か治まってきました。
What was it? I'm alright. Thanks.
なっ　何でだろ。 だっ　大丈夫です　すいません。
Must've been just my imagination. I'm sorry.
何だ　気のせいですよね。 すいません。
-Are you sure? -Are you alright?
（民子）大丈夫？ （真島）大丈夫ですか？
I'm fine. Sorry.
大丈夫　ごめんなさい。
Oh, that's right. I have one apology visit to make.
あっ　そうだ １件　謝罪訪問があったんだ。
Were you scheduled for a visit today, Takagi-kun?
（鮫島）あれ？　高木君　今日 訪問の予定なんかあったっけ。
I took a call from a customer this morning who sounded really mad.
さっき　お客さんから　電話　受けてすごく怒ってらっしゃったんで。
Oh.
（鮫島）ああ。
Oh, then I'll go with you. I have
（真島）あっ　だったら俺も 一緒に行きますよ。　こっちにも→
-one visit to make too. -You.
１件だけあるんで。 お前→
You've been trying to follow me no matter what, huh?
絶対ついてこようとすんな さっきからな。
What? Don't you have to go? -Never mind. Come here for a minute.
（真島）えっ？　ないんすか？ もういい　ちょっと　こっち来い。
What? What is it?
えっ？　何　何すか。
Come here. Let's talk. Come here.
ここ来い　話そう　こっち来い。
Listen, you can't tell anyone, okay?
なあ　誰にも言うなよ。
-Yes. What? -Right now, the twins are...
（真島）はい　えっ？ 今な　うちの双子がな。
I'm going to the stockroom.
（凛花）私 ちょっと　倉庫　行ってきます。
Stockroom? Wait, wait. Why are you going to the stockroom?
倉庫？ ちょちょちょ　何で倉庫に？
I thought I'd replenish the apology gifts.
（凛花）いや おわびの品を補充しようと思って。
I'll go then. Since I'm in charge of the stockroom.
だったら俺が行くよ 倉庫担当だし。
-Was there such a person in charge? -Sure there is. You just don't remember.
そんな担当ありました？ あったじゃん。　覚えてないんだよ。
I'll go, so don't worry. Leave it to the person in charge of the stockroom.
俺が行ってくるから大丈夫。 倉庫担当に任せて。
Kaoru, Tomoki, let's go home.
薫　友樹　帰るぞ。
You've got to be kidding me.
嘘だろ。
Onee-chan, I'm gonna pee in my pants.
お姉ちゃん　おしっこ漏れちゃう。 あ～。
I know, just wait a bit.
分かってるってば ちょっと待ってて。
Hurry.
早く。
Let's go.
行くよ。 うん。　あ～。
Takagi-san, where are the apology gifts? Takagi-san?
（凛花）高木さん　おわびの品は？ 高木さん？
Tomoki, I found the restroom.
友樹　トイレあったよ。
Oh yeah. Thank goodness.
あっ　ホントだ　よかった。
Huh? What?
えっ　えっ？　何？　えっ？
You're Takagi-san's...
あなたたち高木さんの。
Onee-chan, what do we do?
お姉ちゃん　どうしよう。
Tomoki, we're going to run.
友樹　逃げるよ。
Wait, wait. Wait a minute.
（かな）ちょっ　ちょっ えっ　ちょっ　ちょっと待って。→
Wait.
ちょっと待って。
-Why are these children here? -Marumo.
（民子）何で子供がいるの？ マルモ。
-Marumo?
（民子）マルモ？
Hey, hey, you guys.
ちょっ　ちょっと　ちょっ　お前ら。
Kana-san.
（かな）あれ？ かなさん。
Takagi-san, aren't these children your relative's children?
（かな）高木さん　その子たちって 高木さんの親戚のお子さんじゃ。
Takagi-kun, why did you bring the children?
（民子）高木君 何で　子供　連れ込んでんの。
-What's this about? -Um..this is...
（凛花）どういうことですか？ いや　あの　これは。
-I think it's too late for that. -Do you think?
いや　それは　もう　無理ですよ。 やっぱり？
-Yes. -Okay. He says this isn't gonna work anymore.
はい。 あっ　そう。　やっぱ無理だって。
It's too late. Come on out. Let's give up.
無理だって　出ておいで。 諦めよう　もう。
Go on, say your greeting.
ほら　あいさつしなさい。
I'm Sasakura Tomoki. I'm 7 years old. -I'm Sasakura Kaoru, I'm 7 years old.
笹倉　友樹です。　７歳です。 笹倉　薫です。　７歳です。
They're kids of my friend who passed away.
こいつら 亡くなった親友の子供たちで→
I took them in and they're living with me for the time being.
取りあえず　今　俺が引き取って 一緒に住んでるんです。
What? You're the guardian?
（民子）えっ？　親代わり？
Takagi-san's raising the children?
（凛花）高木さん 子育てしてるんですか？
Well, yes.
まあ　うん。
That's so typical of Takagi-kun. People normally won't do such a thing, right?
（鮫島）いや～　高木君らしいな。 普通しないよ。　ねえ。
-This man's not normal. -But why did you bring them here?
変わってるんですよ　この人。 （民子）でも何で連れてきたのよ。
Um...
えっ　え～と。
We're the job exploration team.
私たちは　お仕事調査隊です。
Job exploration team?
（民子）お仕事調査隊？
We came to explore Marumo's job.
マルモのお仕事を調べに来ました。
Does Marumo work hard?
マルモ　ちゃんと働いてますか？
Yes, he always works hard.
（凛花）はい いつも一生懸命ですよ。
I'm really sorry I didn't tell you about them.
あいつらのこと　黙ってて ホントに　すいませんでした。
I just couldn't bear
とにかく　俺→
to see those two, who just lost their father, getting separated.
親を亡くした　あいつらが 引き裂かれるのを見てらんなくて。
I wanted to let them be together at least until they could accept the fact.
せめて　あいつらが納得するまで 一緒にいさせてやりたくて。
I wasn't thinking ahead and it just turned out this way due to circumstances.
先のことなんて何も考えずに 勢いだけで　こうなっちゃって。
I was going to tell you, but
ちゃんと 言うつもりだったんですけど→
I couldn't get myself to say it.
どうしても言えなくて。
You were surprised, weren't you?
驚きましたよね。
I had no intention of deceiving you. My feeling for you is real.
だますつもりはなかったんです。 かなさんへの気持ちは真剣で。
But in the end, I might as well have deceived you.
でも　結局 だましたようなもんですよね。
I'm really sorry.
ホントに　すいません。
It's so like Takagi-san.
高木さんらしいですね。
What?
えっ？
I don't know what lies ahead either, but
先のことなんて 私にも分からないけど→
why don't we just continue dating for the time being?
取りあえず　このまま お付き合い　続けてみましょっか。
-Are you sure? -Yes.
いっ　いいんですか？ はい。
Plus, we haven't even done any couple-like things yet.
あっ　私たち　まだ 恋人らしいこともできてないし。
Yes. Really, thank you.
はい　あの　ホントに よろしくお願いします。
Thank you too.
あっ　よろしくお願いします。
Oh, shoot.
あっ　ヤベえ。 えっ？
I'll be right back after I take the kids home.
ちょっと　俺 ２人のこと　家まで送ってきます。
I'll call you soon.
すぐ　連絡　入れますから。
Hey, you two. Come on, we're going home.
おい　２人　ほら 帰るぞ　うち帰るぞ　うち。
Lunch. What do you want for lunch?
お昼ご飯 お昼ご飯　何がいい　何がいい。
-Hm~. Hamburger. -Hamburger.
う～ん　ハンバーグ。 ハンバーグ。
Okay, hamburger it is.
ＯＫ　ハンバーグ。
-Sorry it took so long. -Where are the twins?
遅くなりました。 （民子）双子ちゃんは？
I took them home.
うちまで送ってきました。
I was fixing their lunch and kinda lost track of time.
昼飯　食わしてたら 何か遅くなっちゃって。
I'm really sorry.
ホントに　すいませんでした。
Really. Why didn't you tell us?
（民子）ホントよ　もう。 何で隠してんのよ。
About the twins.
えっ？ （民子）双子ちゃんのこと。→
We would've cooperated if we knew.
言ってくれれば協力したのに。
I couldn't inconvenience you with my personal situation.
いや　でも　迷惑　掛けるわけにも いかないですし。
You're wrong if you think you can do it all by yourself.
（民子）１人で　できると思ったら 大間違いなんだから。
Make sure you tell us if you need help, okay?
何かあったら言いなさいよ。
Thank you. I'm sorry.
あっ　ありがとうございます。 すいません。
I'll cooperate too. Besides, the twins were so cute.
（凛花）私も協力します。 双子ちゃん　かわいかったし。
Don't be fooled. They could be quite the rascals.
いや～ ２人とも　なかなか　くせ者だよ。
Look, they even came to the office on their own.
勝手に会社まで来ちゃうし。
Sorry for causing a commotion.
お騒がせして　すいませんでした。
It's unheard of.
前代未聞。　ハハハハ。
But you look somewhat relieved.
でも　何か ほっとしたって顔してるよ。
Well, we're all working together anyway
（鮫島）まあ せっかく一緒に働くんだから→
so secrets just get in the way.
隠し事なんて邪魔じゃない。
It's a good thing we found out.
バレて　よかったよね。　ハハ。
Oh, that's right, Takagi-kun.
（鮫島）あっ　そうだ　高木君。
Yes?
何ですか？
About the proposal for Ka-ke Run Run.
（鮫島）かけるんるんの 企画書のことなんだけどさ。
Yes, what about it?
あっ　どうしました？
I showed it to Product Development
あれ　開発の方に見せたら→
and got a pretty good response. Product Development?
結構　反応いいんだよね。 開発？
It's not our standard product, but they were quite interested.
定番商品から　かなり外れてるのに結構　面白がってもらえてさ。
It's a good opportunity. Why don't you polish up your proposal a bit?
せっかくだから もうちょっと練ってみない？
Here you go, Kujira-yu Bowl.
（彩）はい　クジラー油丼。
Itadakima~su.
（友樹・薫）いただきま～す。 （彩）はい。
-Yum. -Really? I'm glad.
（友樹・薫）うまっ。 （彩）ホント？　よかった。
-Here. -Oh, thanks.
（陽介）はい。 あっ　すいません。
What, everyone found out?
（陽介）何　全員にバレちゃったの？
Yes, the whole office at once.
そりゃ　もう　一気にバレましたよ。
What? So what are you gonna do about her?
（陽介）え～。　あっ で　あの　彼女とは　どうすんの？
Of course we're gonna keep on dating.
どうって 続けるに決まってるじゃないすか。
-Is she gonna be alright? -Frankly,
大丈夫なのか？ いや→
I thought we were done.
正直　もう駄目だと思いました。
But Kana-san brought it up and said let's continue.
でもね　かなさんの方から 続けましょうって。
She said we haven't done any couple-like things yet.
あっ　まだ　恋人らしいことも していないしって。
-She said that? -Yes.
向こうから？ はい。
She...how should I put it...has a big heart
もう　何て言うんすか 懐が広いというか→
and is very mature, and wonderful.
人間が　でかいというか すてきというか→
And, I really like her.
もう大好きといった 感じでしょうか。
There he goes again.
また浮かれてる。
Sorry.
すいません。
-We're home.
ただいま。
What? What are you doing, Mook?
あれ？ あれ？　ムック　何してんの？
Give it here. You...what are you doing?
ちょうだい。 おま…　何やってんだよ。
Is that Kaoru's slippers?
それ　薫のスリッパ？
No. Look, they're too big for you, right?
違うよ お前のにしては　でかいだろ？
-Then are they Marumo's? -No, I said.
じゃ　マルモの？ 違うって。
I don't wear these flowery things.
俺は　こんな 花柄なんて履かないよ。
These are special ones for Kana-san.
これは かなさん専用のスリッパなんだ。
Kana-san? Is Kana-san coming?
かなさん？　かなさんが来るの？
Of course she'll be coming.
そりゃ　来るでしょうね。
No one else is wearing slippers.
誰も スリッパなんて履いてないじゃん。
We don't need them. The soles of our feet are dirty already anyway.
俺らはいいんだよ。　もう　すでに 足裏　真っ黒だからな。
But Kana-san's a lady.
かなさんはレディーだから。
Ladies have to protect their feet.
女性は 足を守らないといけないからね。
But Aya-chan don't wear slippers when she comes here.
でも　彩ちゃんは うちでスリッパ履かないよ？
Is Aya-chan a lady? What is she?
彩ちゃんはレディーなのかな あれは何だろうな。
Well, whatever. Anyway, these are Kana-san's slippers.
まあ　いいんだよ。　とにかく これは　かなさんのスリッパ。
You'd better not touch them, okay?
いいか？　触んなよ。
Kana-san...
かなさん…。 [TEL]
Oh, it's a call from Kana-san.
あっ　かなさんから 電話が　かかってきた。
Fancy her calling me at this moment.
こんなことってあるでしょうか。
-Hello? -Takagi-san?
もしもし？ [TEL]（かな）高木さん？
Kana-san, what's up?
かなさん　どうしたんですか？
Takagi-san, are you free this Sunday?
[TEL]高木さん 今度の日曜日　空いてます？
-Sunday?
日曜？
Of course I'm free.
もちろん空いてます。
Good. Then shall we go out?
[TEL]よかった。 だったら　お出掛けしませんか？
Of course. Let's go out.
もちろんですよ　お出掛けか。
Go out? Marumo, are you going out on Sunday?
お出掛け？ マルモ　日曜に　お出掛けするの？
-Sh~sh~sh~. -Maybe a movie?
し～　し～　し～。 [TEL]映画とか。
Um..I'm talking with Kana-san. It's got nothing to do with you guys.
あの　これ　あの　こっちの話だからねっ　お前らに関係ないから。
I want to go on a picnic. I want to take obentou.
薫　ピクニックしたい。 お弁当　持っていく。
I told you already that this has nothing to do with you guys.
だから お前らには関係ないんだっての。
-Is something wrong? -No, I'm sorry.
（かな）どうしたんですか？ [TEL]いや　すいません→
It's nothing.
何でもないですから。
What~ No fair. I want to go on a picnic.
[TEL]え～　つまんない。 [TEL]ピクニックしたい。
You're too noisy. Be quiet, okay?
[TEL]うるさいよ　もう 黙ってろ　なっ。→
Be quiet. Please be quiet. Okay?
静かにして お願い　静かにしてろ　なっ。→
Sorry about all this
すいません　何か→
commotion. Sorry.
ばたばたしちゃって すいません。→
Where shall we go on Sunday?
日曜日　どこ行きましょうか。
Since the twins are looking forward to it too,
あっ　せっかくなんで→
why don't all of us go out together?
双子ちゃんも一緒に お出掛けしませんか？
No. No. That's alright. Really.
いや。　いや　いいですよ　そんな。
Let's do that. The more the merrier.
[TEL]そうしましょうよ。 にぎやかで楽しいじゃないですか。
Are you sure? Thanks.
そうですか？　何か　すいません。
Hey guys, we're going out on Sunday.
お前ら　日曜日　お出掛けするぞ。
Yay~!
（薫・友樹）やった～。
Sorry.
[TEL]すいません。
Please don't mind it.
気にしないでください。
Then I'll call you again.
じゃ また　あらためて　電話しますね。
Here you go.
おなか　すいたな。 （かな）はい　どうぞ。→
Itadakimasu.
（薫・友樹）うわ～。 いただきます。
Help yourself.
（かな）はい　どうぞ。
Cute~.
わ～　カワイイ。
Of course it is since Kana-san made it for us.
かなさんが作ってくれたんだから 当たり前だろ。
-Sorry for making you go through the trouble. -Not at all.
わざわざ　すいません。 いいえ。
-Here. -Yummy.
ほれ。 おいしい。
It's way different from the meals Marumo makes.
マルモが作るご飯とは 全然　違うね。
Marumo's meals are
んっ？ マルモのご飯は→
like more brownish.
もっと茶色い感じだよ。 あら。
Gochisousama.
ごちそうさまでした。
Are you alright? Here you go.
大丈夫ですか？　どうぞ。
It was delicious.
おいしかったです。
Marumo, let's play catch.
マルモ　キャッチボールしようよ。 えっ？
You two go ahead and play without me.
俺はいいから ２人で　やってきなさいよ。
Come on, let's play.
やろうよ。
We practiced by ourselves just like you told us to.
マルモに言われたとおり 自主練したよ。
Get up.
起きて。
Come on, we can do it now.
ねえ　上手になったよ。
Really? Kana-san, why don't you join us too?
ホントか？　お前ら。 あっ　かなさんも　どうですか？
Me too?
えっ　私もですか？
Okay, Kaoru, try throwing to me.
よし　じゃ　薫選手　投げてみよう。
What was that. You're not even close.
あっ　何だよ 全然　駄目じゃねえかよ。
Listen. Keep you face like this. Look straight at the other guy's face.
いいか？　顔は　こう。 相手の顔をちゃんと見る。
Keep your arm like this. Aim it straight at the other person's chest. Got it?
で　手も　こう。　相手の胸んとこな。分かったか。
-Yes, Coach. -Alright.
はい　監督。 よし。
Then throw it towards Kana-san.
じゃ　かなさんの方に投げてみろ。 はい。
Oh, that's pretty good.
おっ　いいじゃねえか。
Okay, Tomoki next. Try to catch.
よし　じゃ　次　友樹　捕ってみろ。 はい。
Here it goes.
（かな）いくよ。　はい。
Oh, nice. Tomoki, nice.
おーっ　ナイス。　友樹　ナイス。
That's good.
いいじゃねえかよ。 イェーイ。
-I want to catch too. -You do? Okay.
薫も捕りたい。 おっ　やるか。　よし。
Here it goes, Kaoru.
じゃ　薫選手　いくぞ。　それ。
Nice, nice. Kaoru nice.
ナイス。　ナイス　薫　ナイス。　ヘイ。
Okay, Tomoki. Tomoki, nice. Tomoki, nice.
よし　友樹。 友樹選手　ナイス。　友樹　ナイス。
You do that very well.
お上手ですね。
Since you made us lunch
お昼 ごちそうになっちゃったんで→
how about having dinner with us at home?
夜は　ぜひ うちで　ご一緒に　どうですか？
But the twins are probably tired too, so we should call it a day.
あっ　でも　双子ちゃんたちも 疲れてるでしょうし　今日は　もう。
They're totally fine. They have endless energy.
全然　大丈夫ですよ。 底無しパワーですから。　ハハ。
-We're back~. -We back.
（薫・友樹）ただいま～。 ただいま。
How was it? Did you have fun at the picnic?
（彩）どうだった？ ピクニック　楽しかった？
It was a lot of fun.
すごく楽しかった。 （彩）うん。
Aya-chan, I'll give you these.
あっ　これ　彩ちゃんにあげる。
Oh, thanks.
（彩）おっ　ありがとう。→
What? Wait. Oh, but all these?
えっ？　いや　ちょっと えっ　でも　こんなに？
You guys brought back all those? From back there?
お前ら　それ持ってきたの？ わざわざ？
It's a present from our outing.
だって　お土産だもん。
Oh, hello.
あっ　あっ　どうも。
-Hello. Good evening. -Good evening.
どうも　こんばんは。 （陽介）こんばんは。
Okay, Kaoru, Tomoki. We're going up.
よし　薫　友樹　上　行くぞ。
Aw~ I wanna eat down here.
え～　僕　下で　ご飯　食べたい。
Kana-san came to have dinner with us, you know.
せっかく かなさん来てくれてんだぞ。
Come on. Don't be like that. Come on, come on.
何　言ってんだよ。 ほら　ほら　ほら　ほら　ほら　ほら。
-Okay. -Let's go, Kana-san.
は～い。 かなさん　どうぞ。
-Oh. -What's wrong?
あっ。 （陽介）どうした。
This. It's for Oyaji-san. -Oh?
これ　親父さんに。 （陽介）えっ？→
-Oh, thanks. -Hey, Kaoru, hurry up.
あっ　サンキュー。 ≪おい　薫　急げ。
-Okay, coming. Wait. -Thanks.
あっ　はい　ちょっと待って　待って。 サンキューな。
Sorry, Sorry. Kana-san, watch your steps.
ごめん　ごめん。 かなさん　階段　気を付けて。
Looks like it's going well, huh?
うまくいってるみたいだね。
-We're home.
ただいま。
Kana-san. Come in. Come in, come in.
かなさん　どうぞ。 どうぞ　どうぞ　どうぞ。
Wait. Just a minute please.
ちょっと ちょっと待ってください。
Please wear this, Kana-san.
かなさん　これ履いてください。
I got it for this day.
この日のために 用意しておきました。
Oh, for me?
（かな）あっ　私のために。
Yes. If you don't wear these, your feet will get all dirty.
はい　これ履かないと　足裏 真っ黒になっちゃいますから。
-Yes, but I feel bad being the only one. -It's alright, it's alright.
（かな）いや　でも　私だけは。 いいんです　いいんです→
It's too late for us, so please don't worry about us and wear them.
俺らは　もう　手遅れですから 遠慮せずに履いてください。
-She's so lucky. -I'll make the dinner so
いいな。 夕飯は俺が作りますから→
Kana-san, please come in and just rest.
かなさん 上がって休んでてください。
-Okay, you guys help me. -Aw~.
よし　お前らも手伝え。 え～。
-No aw-ing. -Okay~.
え～じゃない。 （友樹・薫）は～い。
-Alright. -What shall we make?
よし。 何　作る？
-See if we have any eggs. -Oh? There aren't any.
うん　ちょっと　卵あるか見て。 あれ？　ないよ。
-We don't have eggs. -Excuse me.
んっ？　卵なかった。 あの。
Yes?
はい？
I think I'll leave after all.
今日は　やっぱり失礼します。
What, you're leaving?
えっ　帰るんですか？
Yes, it's getting late too.
はい　もう遅くなっちゃったんで。
-You're leaving? -Yes. I'll see you again. Bye.
もう帰るの？ （かな）うん　またね。　それじゃ。
-Bye bye.
（友樹・薫）バイバイ。 バイバイ。
Kana-san...
行こう。 かなさん　あの。
You okay with that?
いいのか？
Go after her. Act like a man, will you?
行けよ　男だろ？
Kana-san.
かなさん。
Is something wrong?
あの　どうかしましたか？
Oh, sorry. The room was pretty messy, wasn't it?
あっ　すいません 部屋が汚かったですかね。
I should've cleaned it better.
ちゃんと掃除しとけばよかったな。
Maybe we shouldn't have brought those guys with us after all.
あっ　やっぱり　あいつら 連れていかない方がよかったかな。
I think I relied too much on your kindness.
かなさんの言葉に 甘え過ぎちゃったな　俺。
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい。
Why are you apologizing?
どっ　どうして謝るんですか？
I don't think it's going to work.
無理なんじゃないかと思って。
I know I'm the one who said
私から　取りあえず お付き合い　続けましょうなんて→
let's keep on dating for the time being, but
言っちゃいましたけど→
I realized it might be difficult after all.
やっぱり難しいと思うんです。
What? No, it won't be difficult at all.
えっ　そんな そんな　難しくないですよ。
If you're concerned about the twins, I can ask the folks downstairs to watch them,
双子のことだったら　下に 預かってもらうことできるし→
and even if they're left alone, Kaoru's
２人きりにしといても 薫の方なんか→
very mature for her age.
結構しっかりしてるし。
So why don't we leave it as is for now?
だから 取りあえずでいいじゃないですか。
That's what I thought at first too.
そう思ったんですけどね　最初は。
For the time being, we'll just date normally,
取りあえず 普通に　お付き合いして→
like watching movies and going to karaoke.
映画　見たり　カラオケ行ったり。
Movies. Movies will be great.
映画。　いいじゃないですか　映画。
Let's go next time. I'll leave the twins downstairs.
今度　行きましょう。 双子を下に預けて。
I'd like to go to karaoke too. I'm surprisingly good at it.
カラオケ行きたいな。 俺　案外　得意なんですよ。
I realized after spending the day with you all today.
（かな）今日 一緒にいて分かったんです。→
When Takagi-san was with the twins,
私　双子ちゃんと 一緒にいるときの高木さんが→
you looked like their real dad to me.
本当のパパに見えちゃったんです。
I'm not doing as much as you think.
そんな大げさなもんじゃないです。
I just took them in on the spur of the moment
あいつらのこと 勢いで引き取っただけだし→
and although I'm taking care of them, it's like I have no choice.
身の回りのことしてるけど 仕方なくっていうか。
You praise them and scold them without holding anything back.
褒めたり怒ったり 全然　遠慮がなくて→
You're like a real family.
本物の家族みたいで。
Well, not really.
いや　そんな。
Then I felt that
そしたら　やっぱり→
dating "for the time being" was not the solution.
取りあえずでは 済ませられない気がして。
That's...that's not true.
そんな　そんなことないです。
Once I decided that wasn't the solution,
済ませられないって思ったら→
frankly, I knew I wouldn't fit in there.
私は正直 そこには入っていけないなって。
It'll be alright. Today too, we spent the day together.
大丈夫です　今日だって一緒に。
To me, family is something that should be
（かな）私 家族って　一から　ゆっくり→
built slowly, from the beginning.
つくっていくものだって 思うんです。
Well, yes, I understand that, but...
いや　それは　あの。
Even if we continued to date,
（かな）このまま お付き合いを続けても→
later on
後になって→
I'm afraid I might wish
あの子たちがいなければ。→
that those children weren't here.
そんなことを考えちゃいそうで。
I don't want to be like that.
そういうの嫌なんです。
Then, I can send them back to their relatives...
だったら あいつら　また　親戚のところに…。
I guess it's not going to work after all.
やっぱり無理ですよね。
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい。
Welcome.
（陽介）いらっしゃい。
Takagi-san? What's wrong?
（彩）高木さん？ あっ　どうかしたんですか？
Kana-san left.
かなさん帰った。
What?
（彩）えっ？
I've liked Kana-san for a long time.
俺　かなさんのこと ずっと好きでさ。
It's been like many years, you know.
もう何年もだよ。
I persevered and finally got to date her.
頑張って やっと付き合えたのにな。
Did something happen?
何かあったんですか？
I got dumped.
振られた。
What?
えっ？
She thinks a family is something that should be built from the very beginning.
家族は　一から　つくるものだと 思うってさ。
I know that too.
そんなの知ってるよ。
To meet a girlfriend normally, to fall in love and work normally.
普通に彼女つくって 普通に恋愛して　仕事して。
To get married normally and be happy.
普通に結婚して　幸せになってさ。
I used to think that was the natural progression of things too.
俺だって　そういうのが 当たり前だと思ってた。
Ah~. It would've worked out if those guys weren't here.
あ～あ。　あいつら　いなきゃ うまくいってたのに。
-Takagi-san. -Aya.
（彩）ちょっ　高木さん。 （陽介）彩。
Anyway, have a drink.
（陽介）まあ　飲め。
I... I
俺　俺さ→
almost said it.
もうちょっとで 言いそうになっちゃった。
That I was going to take them back.
あいつら返すって。
I'm disgusted with myself.
ホント最低だよな。
But you didn't, did you?
でも言わなかったんだろ？
How can I say that.
言えねえよ。
I can't even imagine such a thing either.
俺　だって　そんなこと そんなこと考えられねえもん。
Mook, come. Come here.
ムック　おいで。 こっち　おいで。
So Mook, you're the guest. Sit there and listen to us, okay?
それじゃ　ムックは　お客さんね。 そこに座って聞いててね。
Job exploration team, gather.
お仕事調査隊　集合。
-Roger. -Hey, hey. What are you standing on.
ラジャー。 ちょちょちょ　どこ乗ってんだよ。
-Oh, sorry, but... -No but's.
あっ　ごめんなさい　でも。 でもじゃねえの。
I'm sorry.
ごめんなさい。
What do you guys have in your hands?
お前ら　それ　何　持ってんだ？
Our report on the job exploration.
お仕事調査隊の報告書です。
We got a gold star for it and we wanted to read it to you
花丸もらったから 読んであげようと思って→
so we were practicing.
それで練習してたんだけど。
So that's what you were doing.
そうなのか。
But you shouldn't stand on the table.
でもテーブルの上は駄目だろ。
Let me hear it then.
じゃ　ちょっと　聞かしてみろ。
Sit there then.
じゃ　そこに座って。
"Marumo's job is bunbougu-ya-san."
「マルモのお仕事は 文房具屋さんです」
"He leaves the house at 7:50 every morning."
「毎日７時５０分に家を出ます」
"On the way, he drinks coffee to get his energy."
「途中でコーヒーを飲んで 元気を出します」
"He's not good at throwing away the empty can,
「空き缶を捨てるのは下手だけど→
but he doesn't give up until it goes into the trash can."
ちゃんと入るまで 投げて　諦めません」
"Marumo's job at the company
あっ。 「マルモの会社のお仕事は→
is to study and get scolded."
お勉強をしたり 怒られたりすることです」
"When he answers the phone, Marumo does his best to apologize."
「電話が　かかってきたら マルモは頑張って謝ります」
"He apologizes many times."
「何回も謝ります」
"But he still gets scolded."
「それでも　まだ怒られます」
"That's why I think I'll apologize with him next time."
「だから今度は僕も一緒に 謝ってあげようと思いました」
Study and get scolded. What kind of a job is that.
ハハ　勉強して怒られて どんな仕事だよ。
Trade places now.
じゃ　交代。 うん。
"Marumo also has another job."
「あと マルモの仕事は　まだあります」
"He has a job to make our dinner when he comes home from work."
「会社から帰ったら 私たちのご飯を作る仕事です」
"The meals that Marumo makes
「マルモが作るご飯は→
are always brownish and salty and delicious."
いつも　茶色くて　しょっぱくて おいしいです」
"When he doesn't go to work and has a day off,
「会社じゃない休みのときは→
he also does the laundry and sewing."
お洗濯をしたり お裁縫のお仕事もします」
"But he's lousy at his job of cleaning the house,
「でも 掃除のお仕事は下手くそで→
so Marumo and Kaoru and Tomoki all have dirty feet."
マルモも薫も友樹も 足の裏が真っ黒です」
"The job at Akebono Offices Supplies is like a father's,
「あけぼの文具のお仕事は お父さんみたいで→
and the job at home is like a mother's."
おうちのお仕事は お母さんみたいです」
"I thought he must have his hands full with both jobs."
「両方で大変だと思いました」
"I want to say thank you to Marumo
「マルモは たくさんお仕事をして→
for working so many jobs."
ありがとうと言いたいと 思いました」
"When I grow up
「私も大きくなったら→
I want to work many jobs like Marumo."
マルモみたいに たくさんお仕事したいです」
"The end."
「終わり」
But I don't consider it my job to make you guys' meals, you know.
でも　お前らの飯　作るのは 仕事じゃねえぞ。
-It's not? -No, it's not.
違うの？ うん　違うよ。
What should we do? We made a mistake.
どうしよう　調査隊　間違えた。
Marumo, why are you crying? Is it because we made a mistake?
マルモ　どうして泣いてるの？ 間違えちゃったから？
Thanks, exploration team.
調査隊　ありがとな。
Really, thanks.
ホッ　ホントありがとう。
Marumo.
マルモ。
I'm happy for you.
よかったな。
Thanks. Thanks.
ありがとう。　ありがとう。
House cleaning must be done properly!
そうじは　ちゃんとすること！
Keep the soles of your feet clean!
え～　よし。　足ウラせいけつ！
Bye bye, slippers!
バイバイ　スリッパ！
-Okay, we're gonna clean the house now. -Bye bye slippers?
よし　今から掃除するぞ。 バイバイ　スリッパ？
Why bye bye?
何でバイバイなの？
We don't need fancy things like slippers in our house.
うちにな　スリッパなんて上等な物必要ねえんだ。
-Aren't you throwing it away? -Huh?
捨てないの？ えっ？
What...what do you mean? I'm throwing it away...now.
いや　なっ　何　言ってんの 捨てるよ　今。
Throw it away. Yeah. Throw it away.
捨てる　うん 捨てる　捨てるんだよ　これ。
Okay, that's it. This is the way it should be.
よし　これでよし これでいいんだ　うん。
Okay, guys, let's begin.
よし　お前ら　掃除を始めるぞ。
Roger.
（薫・友樹）ラジャー。
Here we go.
いくぞ。 （薫・友樹）おう。
Okay. Mook, you do it too.
よし。　おう　ムックも　やれ。
Why are you coming to me?
何で俺んとこ来んだよ　お前。
Do it right, from corner to corner, side to side.
端まで　端まで 端までな　ちゃんと。
Here we go. On your mark.
いくぞ。 用意。
Get set. Go.
どん。